studyguideindia.com 2009-08-22

# Studyguideindia.com | Study Guidance, guide, list of colleges, university, universities, management, law, legal, polytechnic, diploma, study abroad, engineering, colleges in India, education news, education loan, education scholarship, women's college, distance education, career news, teacher training, pin code, STD / ISD codes, campus interview, English grammar, education articles.

**Collection of your Personal Information**

We will ask you time to time to enter or update your personal information which identifies you or allows us to contact you to provide a service or carry out a transaction that you have requested. The service may include receiving information about **StudyGuideIndia.com** products and services, entering a contest, ordering e-mail newsletters, joining a limited-access premium site or service, signing up for an event or training, or when purchasing, downloading and/or registering **StudyGuideIndia.com** products. The personal information we collect may include your name, title, college, course,company or organization name, work e-mail, work phone, work or home address, information about your job function and information about your company.

The site may collect certain information about your visit, such as the name of the Internet service provider, the Internet Protocol (IP) address, the date and time you access the website, the pages that you access when you use the site, and the Internet address of the website from which you linked directly to our site. This information is used to help improve the Site, analyze trends, and administer the Site.

Refer a Friend: You can choose the option to invite your friend(s) to **StudyGuideIndia.com** or you can send the URL of any interesting article/content you liked in **StudyGuideIndia.com**. **StudyGuideIndia.com** will record such referrals to create up to 3 reminders on your behalf.

**StudyGuideIndia.com** technical communities provide opportunities to interact with **StudyGuideIndia.com** employees, experts, and your peers in order to share knowledge and news about **StudyGuideIndia.com** products and related technologies. In order to avoid your e-mail address or other personal information from being gathered and used by others for inappropriate or harmful purposes, **StudyGuideIndia.com** advises that you should be cautious about posting a real e-mail address or other personal information to newsgroups, chats, or other public forums.

**Use of your Personal Information:**

The personal information collected on this Site will be used to operate the Site and to provide the service(s) or carry out the transaction(s) you have requested or authorized.

In support of these uses, **StudyGuideIndia.com** may use personal information to provide you with more effective customer service, to improve the Site and any related **StudyGuideIndia.com** products or services, and to make the Site easier to use by eliminating the need for you to repeatedly enter the same information or by customizing the Site to your particular preference or interests. In order to offer you a more consistent experience in your interactions with **StudyGuideIndia.com** , information collected by **StudyGuideIndia.com** may be combined with information collected by other **StudyGuideIndia.com** services.

We may use your personal information to provide you with important information about the product or service that you are using, including critical updates and notifications. Additionally, with your permission, we may send you information about other **StudyGuideIndia.com** products and services, and/or share information with **StudyGuideIndia.com** partners so they may send you information about their products and services.

We merge site-visitation data with anonymous demographic information for research purposes, and we may use this information in aggregate to provide more relevant content. In some limited-entry sections of **StudyGuideIndia.com** , with your approval, we will combine site-visitation data with your personal information in order to provide you with personalized content. If you decline permission, we will not provide you the personalized service and won't merge your personal information with site-visitation data.

When you sign up for a newsletter or agree to receive promotional e-mail, **StudyGuideIndia.com** may use customized links or similar technologies to track e-mail links that you click. We may associate that information with your personal information in order to provide you more focused e-mail communications or purchase information. Each e-mail communication includes an unsubscribe link allowing you to stop delivery of that type of communication.

Some services on **StudyGuideIndia.com** offer individuals the ability to publicly display certain personal information, such as for a **StudyGuideIndia.com** partner who wishes to publish contact information as part of offering a business service. Participation in such services is always optional.

**StudyGuideIndia.com** occasionally hires other companies to provide limited services on our behalf, such as Web site hosting, packaging, mailing and delivering prizes, answering customer questions about products and services, and sending information about our products, special offers, and other new services. We will only provide those companies the personal information they need to deliver the service. They are required to maintain the confidentiality of the information and are prohibited from using that information for any other purpose.

**StudyGuideIndia.com** may disclose personal information if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on **StudyGuideIndia.com** or the Site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of **StudyGuideIndia.com** and our family of Web sites; or (c) act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of **StudyGuideIndia.com** employees or agents, users of **StudyGuideIndia.com** products or services, or members of the public.

Personal information collected on the Site may be stored and processed in India or any other country in which **StudyGuideIndia.com** or its affiliates, subsidiaries or agents maintain facilities, and by using the Site, you consent to any such transfer of information outside of your country.

**Control of your Personal Information:**

Except as otherwise described in this statement, personal information you provide on the Site will not be shared outside of **StudyGuideIndia.com** and its controlled subsidiaries and affiliates without your permission. As described below in the next section, you can access your personal information and make choices about how you wish to be contacted.

Please be aware that this privacy statement and any choices you make on the Site will not necessarily apply to personal information you may have provided to **StudyGuideIndia.com** in the context of other, separately operated, **StudyGuideIndia.com** products or services.

**StudyGuideIndia.com** may send out periodic e-mails informing you of technical service or security issues related to a product or service you requested, or confirming you requested a product or service. In some services offered by **StudyGuideIndia.com** , contact with the customer is an intrinsic part of the service. You will not be able to choose to unsubscribe to these mailings, as they are considered an essential part of the service(s) you have chosen.

**Security of your Personal Information:**

**StudyGuideIndia.com** is committed to protecting the security of your personal information. We use a variety of security technologies and procedures to help protect your personal information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. For example, we store the personal information you provide on computer servers with limited access that is located in controlled facilities. Additionally, when we transmit sensitive personal information (such as a credit card number) over the Internet, we protect it through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.

**Acceptance of Terms/Changes to our Privacy Policy:**

Using **StudyGuideIndia.com** will assume that you accept the privacy policy of this site. When we use any third party for any affiliated service, the third party privacy policy also applicable to you by using this site.

If you have any questions or concerns, feel free to contact us at: [info@StudyGuideIndia.com](mailto:info@studyguideindia.com)
